Guide to the Bob Fitch Photography Archive M1994
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Subject Files, 1960-2016; 23 Linear Feet 43 manuscript boxes
  - Leway, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    Unidentified people, part of Leway Incorporated (Asian-American self-help youth group) at Fountain of Youth ice cream parlor/pool hall and other Chinatown businesses, San Francisco, California, photographed by Bob Fitch.
    Contact sheets are numbered 904, 907-909, 915-919.
  - Lemon, Bob [contact sheets], 1960-2016 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Leor, Andrea: 50th birthday party [contact sheets], October 3, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    Contact sheet is numbered 6200.
  - Lindsay family [contact sheets], 2001 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    Contact sheets are numbered 6017-6022.
  - Lindsey, "Holy" Hubert, University of California Berkeley campus, Berkeley, California [contact sheets], 1973 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    Contact sheet is numbered 3658.
  - Lofton, Melissa [contact sheets], 2004 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    Contact sheet is numbered 6123.
  - Lord, Jack [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    Contact sheet is numbered 2424.
  - Lucken, Claudi [contact sheets, prints and negatives], September, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Luterman, Ali [contact sheets], 2004 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    Poet Alison Luterman with Susan-Jane Harrison, Cathleen Riddley, Deb Fink, Louis Lansman and Naomi Newman reading scripts for a play.
    Contact sheets are numbered 6168-6170.
  - Luterman, Ali [prints], 1999 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Maher, Kathleen [contact sheets], 1973 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    Contact sheet is numbered 3892.
  - Makonde sculpture [contact sheets], 1968 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    Contact sheets are numbered 620-623.
  - Male secretary, New York City, New York [contact sheets], January 11, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    Contact sheet is numbered 3617.
  - Mallory, Karen [contact sheets] [RESTRICTED], 2000 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    Contact sheet is numbered 5990.
  - Marches, demonstrations and crowds [prints], 1960-2004 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    Prints are numbered 183, 185, 227, 246, 340, 408, 424, 567, 568, 573, 583, 596, 611, 614, 616, 703, 704, 708, 711, 721, 744, 760, 774, 3127, 3132, 3279, 3280, 3311, 3315, 3424, 3502, 3503, 3505, 4186, 4195, 6129, 6131.
  - Mariachi band: Benefit for Jackie Suazo - Santa Fe County Sheriff candidate, Santa Fe, New Mexico [slides], 1974 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Mariante, Benjamin, Reverend: "Obscene" hippie poster [contact sheets and notes], April, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    Contact sheet is numbered 182.
  - Mars-Catini wedding [negatives], July 23, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Marshall, Jim [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2775.
  - Martinez, Betita [contact sheets], April, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4254.
  - MASC [theatre] [contact sheets], 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    Contact sheets are numbered 943, 963-970.
  - McCloud River Railroad [McCloud Railway], McCloud California [contact sheets], September, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5541, 5542.
  - McCrary wedding [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Contact sheet is numbered 2796.
  - McCullum [contact sheets], 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Contact sheet is numbered 544.
  - McManus, Phil [contact sheets], 2004 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Contact sheets are numbered 6164, 6165.
  - Meade, Ken [contact sheets], February 4, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2561-2568.
  - Meat in grocery stores and Kiri [contact sheets], March, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3698.
  - Men [prints], 1965-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Prints are numbered 122, 130, 148, 189, 203, 283, 298, 312, 328, 334, 357, 448, 469, 472, 475, 754, 763, 822, 848, 937, 941, 945, 955, 960, 1605, 1608, 1610, 1624, 1856, 1872, 2012, 2330, 2815, 2921, 3194, 3268, 3314, 3482, 3548, 3570, 3582, 3609, 3610, 3611, 3612, 3617, 3622, 3628, 3692, 3718, 3749, 3750, 3780, 3839, 3879, 4065, 4067, 4096, 4136, 4200, 4234, 4277, 4302.
  - Methodist Women Conference [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1599, 1603, 1605-1607, 1610, 1617, 1750, 1751, 1752.
  - Methodist Youth [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1868-1874.
  - Mexico-America for Democracy Tour [slides], July, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Mexico elections [contact sheets], July, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5789, 5790, 5796-5799.
  - Mexico [slides], December, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - MGM [contact sheets], 1976 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4502, 4503, 4521.
  - Minolta test [contact sheets], March, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1611, 1612.
  - Miscellaneous [contact sheets], 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    Contact sheets are numbered 122, 132, 156, 178, 179, 196, 200, 225, 257, 291, 306, 307, 323, 356, 610, 1457, 1581, 3137, 3144.
  - Miscellaneous [prints], 1960-2016 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous [copy negatives], 1960-2016 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous images for Stanford web [slides], 1970-2002 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous oversized photos [prints], 1965-1973 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    Prints are numbered 120, 122, 148, 206, 224, 254, 279, 297, 389, 392, 442, 466, 470, 530, 540, 567, 568, 572, 590, 591, 691, 700, 751, 754, 822, 861, 3118, 3418, 3498, 3577, 3582, 3585, 3769, 3972, 3974, 3976, 3976, 4070.
  - Mission Switchboard, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    Contact sheets are numbered 881-884.
  - Model United Nations, New York City, New York [contact sheets], 1972 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3400-3403.
  - Models [contact sheets], 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Contact sheet is numbered 639.
  - Montclair sanctuary presentation [contact sheets], June, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3426, 3427, 3471.
  - Monterey Bay Central Labor Council: Anniversary dinner with Dolores Huerta, Monterey, California [contact sheets], 2003 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Contact sheet is numbered 6107.
  - Monterey Contra musicians, Monterey, California [contact sheets], March 7, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Contact sheet is numbered 6121.
  - Morgan, John Alan: Graduation [contact sheets], June, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    John Alan Morgan and Temple [Morgan?]. See also John and Temple folder.
    Contact sheets are numbered 1533, 2851.
  - Moscone, George [contact sheets], 1973 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4074-4078.
  - Moses Hall occupation, University of California Berkeley campus, Berkeley, California [contact sheets], October, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Contact sheets are numbered 698, 699.
  - Motorcycle riders, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], February, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Contact sheet is numbered 3272.
  - Mount Shasta, California [contact sheets], 1978 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    Contact sheet is numbered 5525.
  - Mount Shasta, California: Black Butte [contact sheets], December, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    Contact sheet is numbered 5729.
  - The Movement [slides], 1965-1977 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - The Movement: Documentary of a Struggle for Equality by Lorraine Hansberry [book], 1964 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Mudball, Oakland, California [contact sheets], 1967 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Contact sheets are numbered 832-841.
  - Mudflat sculptures, Emeryville, California [contact sheets], 1966-1971 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    Contact sheets are numbered 174, 175, 177, 3247, 3248.
  - Mudpuddle boats, Oakland, California [contact sheets], 1967 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Contact sheets are numbered 832-834.
  - Multi media class [contact sheets], January, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4129.
  - Musicians [prints], 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    Prints are numbered 905, 3775, 3776, 3780.
  - Musicians [slides], 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - My Eyes Have Seen: Notes, 1967-1971 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    My eyes have seen, the book created using notes and images found in this file, has been digitized and can be viewed through this link:
    https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/10457926
  - My Eyes Have Seen: Coretta Scott King and Martin Luther King Junior's funeral [prints], 1967-1971 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - My Eyes Have Seen: David Harris' release from prison [prints], 1967-1971 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - My Eyes Have Seen: Pete Seeger, David Harris, and Joan Baez [prints], 1967-1971 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - My Eyes Have Seen: Ron Dellums [prints], 1967-1971 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - My Eyes Have Seen: United Farm Workers [prints], 1967-1971 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - My Eyes Have Seen: Catholic Worker [prints], 1967-1971 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - My Eyes Have Seen: The South [prints], 1967-1971 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - My Eyes Have Seen: Berrigan Brothers [prints], 1967-1971 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - My Eyes Have Seen [slides] [part 1 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - My Eyes Have Seen [slides] [part 2 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - New Mexico: Native American protest, Farmington, New Mexico [contact sheets], May, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4192, 4193, 4196, 4200-4205, 4209.
  - New Mexico: Native American protest, Farmington, New Mexico [prints], May, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Prints are numbered 4194, 4196, 4198-4202, 4204, 4207-4209, 4223, 4226.
  - New Mexico: Native American protest, Farmington, New Mexico [slides], May, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - New Mexico: Native American protest, Farmington, New Mexico: Images for Stanford web [slides], May, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - New Mexico: Tierra Amarillo co-operative [contact sheets and notes], May, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4213, 4214.
  - New Mexico: Tierra Amarillo clinic [slides], May, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - New Mexico: El Rito - Bob Garcia [contact sheets], May, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4227-4235, 4250.
  - New Mexico: El Rito [slides], May, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - New Mexico: El Rito [slides], May, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - New Mexico: Santa Fe murals [contact sheets], May, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4236-4243, 4357.
  - New Mexico: Santa Fe murals [slides], May, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - New Mexico: Montegue family [contact sheets], May, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4248.
  - New Mexico: Santa Fe people [contact sheets], May, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4251.
  - New Mexico: Vallecitos farming [contact sheets], May, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4252.
  - New York City streets [contact sheets], 1972 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Contact sheet is numbered 3358.
  - "No Government…" bumper sticker [contact sheets], April, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4167.
  - Nonviolent Peaceforce: Photo identifications, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Nonviolent Peaceforce: Notes, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Nonviolent Peaceforce: Sri Lanka trip [notes], 2005 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Nora and Shelley [contact sheets], January, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3614-3616, 3619.
  - Noriega family [contact sheets], December, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4361.
  - North Oakland parish, Oakland, California [contact sheets], 1966-1968 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    Contact sheets are numbered 379, 381, 382, 384, 414, 426-429, 431, 448, 469, 470, 472, 480, 481, 585, 675.
  - Northern California Savings [contact sheets], 1975 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4390.
  - Oakland, California [contact sheets], 1966-1968 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    Contact sheets are numbered 168, 169, 191, 275, 282, 290, 318, 322, 326, 354, 366, 368, 369, 371, 375, 380, 383, 386, 387, 390, 433, 603.
  - Oakland City Council, Oakland, California [contact sheets], 1968 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    Contact sheets are numbered 516, 520, 524, 526, 527, 640.
  - Oakland Economic Development Council Incorporated [OEDCI], Oakland, California [contact sheets], 1966-1968 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    Contact sheets are numbered 452, 454, 455, 476, 504, 507, 523, 525.
  - Oakland Education, Oakland, California [contact sheets], 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    Contact sheet is numbered 758.
  - Oakland Army Induction Center Demonstration, Oakland, California [contact sheets], December 18, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    Contact sheets are numbered 419-425.
  - Oakland Police hearing, Oakland, California [contact sheets], 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    Contact sheets are numbered 737-741, 743-747.
  - Oakland skyline, Oakland, California [contact sheets], 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2679, 3624.
  - Oakland Zoo, Oakland, California [contact sheets], March 18, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3693, 3694.
  - Old people [prints], 1965-1973 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    Prints are numbered 113, 219, 3095, 3118, 3253, 3605.
  - Office and Technical Employees Union, Oakland, California [contact sheets], September 3, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4022-4028.
  - Omstead, Robert, Reverend: Induction [contact sheets and notes], 1966-1969 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    Contact sheets are numbered 357, 753-756, 759-761, 763, 807, 808.
  - Om Hollow Commune [contact sheets], 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    Contact sheets are numbered 934, 936-942, 944, 948, 950, 955, 960.
  - Organizer workshop [notes], 2006 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Organizing For Our Lives: New Voices From Rural Communities by Richard Street, Newsage Press and CRLA [book], 1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Pacific Gas and Electric: Moss Landing [contact sheets], 1973 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4398.
  - Pacific Lutheran Theological Seminary, Berkeley, California [contact sheets], January 31, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4125.
  - Pacific School of Religion, Berkeley, California [contact sheets and notes], 1968 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Contact sheets are numbered 650-674, 692, 693.
  - Pacific School of Religion, Berkeley, California [copy negatives], 1968 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Pacific School of Religion: Reverend Bunyan Davie Napier installation, Berkeley, California [contact sheets and notes], October 6, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3519-3521.
  - Palestine trip [contact sheets and notes], July, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5998-6014.
  - Palestine [prints], July, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Prints are numbered 5998-6002.
  - Palestine [prints], July, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    Prints are numbered 6003-6008.
  - Palestine [prints], July, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    Prints are numbered 6001, 6004, 6007, 6009-6014.
  - Palmer, Tim [contact sheets], March 17, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5738, 5739.
  - Paloni-Scalese wedding [negatives], 1960-2016 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Parker induction [contact sheets], 1968 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Contact sheets are numbered 703, 704.
  - Parks, Rosa [contact sheets], January, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4362, 4363.
  - Patty [prints], 1993 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Prints are numbered 5842.
  - Peace [notes], 2002-2006 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Peace Brigade [contact sheets], 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3539, 4105.
  - Peace march: Sacramento, California [slides], 1985 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Peace march: Sacramento Religious Community for Peace, Sacramento, California [contact sheets], April 1, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5751-5754.
  - Peace march: Sacramento Religious Community for Peace, Sacramento, California [contact sheets], March 24, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5749, 5750.
  - Peace march: San Francisco, California [contact sheets], April 15, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 181, 183-187, 192.
  - Peace march: San Francisco, California [contact sheets], April 24, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2783-2785.
  - Peace march: San Francisco, California [slides], 1973 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Peace march: San Francisco, California [contact sheets], May 20, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    Contact sheets are numbered 6128-6131.
  - Peace march: San Francisco, California and Washington D.C. [slides], 1973 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Peace march: San Francisco, California and Washington D.C.: Images for Stanford web [slides], 1973 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Peace Movement [contact sheets], 1967 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    Contact sheets are numbered 408-411.
  - Peace Nine, Fellowship Of Reconciliation [FOR] [contact sheets], 1968 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    Contact sheets are numbered 611, 614, 630.
  - Peace sign, Mudflats, Emeryville, California [contact sheets], 1968-1969 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    Contact sheets are numbered 824, 871-873.
  - People [slides], 1967-1974 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - People's Union [contact sheets], May, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    Members of the People's Union holding meetings and doing repairs at a house, photographed by Bob Fitch. Include images of David Harris, Joan Baez and others. The People's Union was a Palo Alto based anti-war group that also ran a co-operative farm in the San Joaquin valley.
    Contact sheets are numbered 2776, 2797, 2798, 2800, 2801.
  - People's Union [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    Members of the People's Union at meetings, playing basketball and doing gymnastics, at the intentional community Struggle Mountain and other locations, photographed by Bob Fitch. Includes images of David Harris, Joan Baez, Allen Ginsberg and others.
    Contact sheets are numbered 2853, 2854, 2856, 2861, 2867-2869, 2874, 3126, 3213, 3214, 3217.
  - People's Union: Farm, Fresno, California [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    Contact sheet is numbered 2892.
  - People's Union: Farm, Fresno, California [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3129-3131, 3135, 3145, 3284-3290.
  - People's Union: Propaganda Brigade San Francisco Airport Hilton [contact sheets], May 30, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2820, 2821.
  - People's Union: July Fourth practice at Struggle Mountain [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    Contact sheet is numbered 2893.
  - People's Union: Rainbow and Willow [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    Contact sheet is numbered 3254.
  - People's Union: San Francisco teach-in, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], February, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    Contact sheets are numbering 3265, 3268.
  - People's Union: David Harris' home, Woodside, California [slides], May 15, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Photography workshop [contact sheets], December, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    Contact sheet is numbering 4102.
  - The Pill [contact sheets], 1967 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    Contact sheet is numbered 236.
  - Pinkard, Frank [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    Contact sheets are numbering 2525-2528, 2594.
  - Pinkard, Frank [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    Contact sheets are numbering 2675-2678.
  - Pinkard, Frank: Campaign for Oakland City Council [contact sheets], January 30, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    Contact sheets are numbering 2544-2546, 2548, 2551, 2553-2555, 2557, 2558.
  - Planet USA [contact sheets], March 6, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    Contact sheets are numbered 6119-6122.
  - PMC [contact sheets], July 19, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4277.
  - Point Reyes, California [contact sheets], 1972 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3418-3421.
  - Police dune buggy, Malibu, California [contact sheets], September 6, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4032.
  - Police and military [prints], 1967-1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Prints are numbered 397, 724, 2121, 2981, 2984, 3121, 3122, 3125, 3127, 3596, 3618, 3675, 4113, 4117, 4119-4121, 4522.
  - Poor People's March, Washington D.C. [contact sheets], 1968 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Also includes images from DeFremery Park, Oakland, California.
    Contact sheets are numbered 521, 528, 531, 532, 536, 538, 539.
  - Posters: Martin Luther King Jr. standing in front of Gandhi picture and Daniel Berrigan flashing peace sign while handcuffed [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Contact sheet is numbered 1006.
  - Potter art [contact sheets], 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Contact sheet is numbered 319.
  - Powell, Adam Clayton: Speaking at the University of California Berkeley, Berkeley, California [contact sheets], 1967 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Contact sheets are numbered 474, 475, 477-479.
  - Powell, Adam Clayton: Speaking at the University of California Berkeley, Berkeley, California [prints], 1967 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Prints are numbered 474.
  - Power to the People: Active Nonviolence in the United States [negatives], 1960-2016 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Negatives from the book, "The Power of the People: Active Nonviolence in the United States". The book edited by Robert Cooney and Helen Michalowski. Bob Fitch helped advise on the project.
  - Powers, John: Sanctuary [contact sheets], April, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3327-3332, 3334.
  - Primary Care Associate Program: Stanford University, Foothill College and San Francisco General Hospital [contact sheets] [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4290, 4292, 4294, 4297-4300, 4309, 4310, 4523.
  - Primary Care Associate Program, Stanford Medical Center: Slideshow with script [slides] [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Primary Care Associate Program, Stanford Medical Center: Slideshow [cassette] [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    Materials in this file are restricted until January 1, 2050.
  - Rachael [contact sheets], 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1158-1169.
  - Rainbow Family of Living Light: Rainbow Gathering, near Pass Creek, Shoshone National Forest, Wyoming [contact sheets and notes], July 4, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3876, 3877.
  - Rainbow Family of Living Light: Rainbow Gathering, near Pass Creek, Shoshone National Forest, Wyoming [slides], July 4, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Ramon: Chico, California [contact sheets], 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    Contact sheets are numbered 892-901, 920.
  - Rasbach, Mark [contact sheets], 1972 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3533, 3568.
  - Reber, Carol [contact sheets], November, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4095.
  - Red Buddha Theatre, San Francisco, California [contact sheets and program], October 1, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4040-4044.
  - Redwoods and roots [contact sheets], April 6, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4176, 4177.
  - Reich, Cristi [contact sheets and prints], 2000 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5954, 5966, 5967, 5979.
  - Reich, Cristi [contact sheets] [RESTRICTED], 2000 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    Materials in this file are restricted until January 1, 2080.
    Contact sheets are numbered 5966, 5967.
  - Reich-Strauss wedding, Lincoln, Massachusetts [printed contact sheets and notes], July 25, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Religious/religion [prints], 1966-1973 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    Prints are numbered 175, 289, 724, 1725, 1819, 1840, 1873, 3210, 3311, 3315, 3548, 3570, 3579, 3628, 3790.
  - Religious sign [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Contact sheet is numbered 1408.